Okay.
another monday bells are ringing loud lost
inside a noisy shuffling crowd there's josh
reilly king of the obscene make another ugly
little scene he thinks he's tough he thinks he's
cool breaking every single golden rule but here
she comes the final word the quiet call before
the storm is heard and that demarco decree comes
raining down on the baddest saddest bully in
this town another week of picking up the trash
another lesson in a brilliant flash And I catch
your eye across the floor We've seen this happen
here before
He doesn't learn, he never will He's standing on
the same old hill A pointless pride and cheap
shot lies right there before our watching eyes
Justice here is swift and true for me and
especially for you The gavel falls, the
sentence read The words that fill us both with
dread are not for us And the DeMarco Decree comes
raining down on the baddest, saddest bully in
this town. Another week of picking up the trash.
Another lesson in a brilliant flash. And I catch
your eye across the floor. We've seen this
happen here before.
♪
And the Demarco decree comes raining down on the
baddest, saddest bully in this town. Another
week of picking up the trash. Another lesson in a
brilliant flash. And I catch your eye across the
floor. We've seen this happen here before.
um